### Contact

ericwhite0703@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/eric-white-58657b34 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Public Speaking Customer Service Management

#### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

# **Eric White**

Registered Nurse, CCRN Intensive Care Unit (ICU) Tri-City Medical Center

Escondido, California

## Summary

I am a nurse who loves to learn and help others do the same. A great teacher helps student learn how to think, not simply teach them what to think. With so much to learn I want to reinforce the humanity of those we care for. We need to know how to perform assessments and implement treatments, but also have a spirit of inquiry and reflection. This drives us to ask why, how, when, with the hopes of uncovering new pathways towards better outcomes.

Tri-City Medical Center, Oceanside, CA September 2017 to present Intensive Care Unit – Registered Nurse

- Provide superior professional care utilizing diverse modalities for a diverse population of patients (CHF, CABG, CRRT, Acute MI, IABP, complex neurological and respiratory, EVD, ARDS, Sepsis, and other medical/surgical conditions)
- Maintain professional standards of conduct and ethics as outlined in department expectations and professional organization
- Serve as preceptor and mentor for graduating RN students four week capstone clinical experience
- Recipient of the 2019 ICU Professional Practice award
- Active participant in ICU Council

Tri-City Medical Center, Oceanside, CA August 2016 - August 2017 2P MedSurg/Oncology – Registered Nurse

 2017 Certificate of Leadership Award for advancing the profession of nursing through passion, quality, communication, team building, creativity, flexibility and promoting a healthy work environment

Education
Palomar College
December 2015
Associate of Science, Nursing (ADN)

- Alumni Advisor of Peer-2-Peer Mentor Program
- Committee Member, Recruitment and Retention Committee
- Scholarship recipient from San Diego Foundation, Assistance League of Inland North County, Family of Sam and Rose Stein, Student Nurses Association of Palomar, and President's Associates Welcome Back to School

Biola University
December 2009
Bachelor of Science, Organizational Leadership (BSOL)

## Experience

Tri-City Medical Center
4 years 5 months

- Student Leadership Council Member

Registered Nurse, CCRN - Intensive Care Unit (ICU) September 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months) Oceanside, California

- -Provide superior professional care utilizing diverse modalities for a diverse population of patients (Atrial Fibrilation, CHF, CABG, CRRT, Acute MI, IABP, complex neurological, respiratory failure and ARDS, Sepsis, and other medical/surgical conditions)
- -Engage in dialogue to identify and address concerns of patient and families
- -Drive collaboration between disciplines and maintain open lines of communication
- -Prioritize and respond appropriately to requests in high stress situations
- -Maintain composure and problem solving focus during stressful interactions
- -2019 ICU Professional Practice award and July 2019 ICU Employee of the Month
- -2017 Leadership Award for advancing the profession of nursing through passion, quality, communication, team building, creativity, flexibility and promoting a healthy work environment
- -Maintain professional standards of conduct and ethics as outlined in department expectations and professional organization
- -Serve as preceptor and mentor for senior RN students

Registered Nurse - MedSurg/Oncology August 2016 - August 2017 (1 year 1 month) Lift Team Tech - Intensive Care Unit March 2016 - July 2016 (5 months) Oceanside

Dependable Nursing Registered Nurse - Field Visits May 2016 - July 2016 (3 months)

Carlsbad

NewSchool of Architecture + Design Administrative Assistant January 2014 - October 2014 (10 months) San Diego

- Collaborated with department chair on planning and implementing policies and initiatives
- Assisted with department budgeting models
- Created quality measurement tools for accreditation reports and trained faculty on their use
- Planned and supported staff, committee and advisory board meetings

eChristian, Inc 5 years 5 months

Production Manager

January 2010 - August 2013 (3 years 8 months)

- Managed and prioritized 100-150 recording projects annually
- Improved financial management and outcomes for each project
- Hired and motivated actors, studio managers, engineers and other contractors
- Formalized training process for quality improvement
- Negotiated with and secured new vendors for services and supplies Results:
- Developed workflow improvements decreasing time required for individual project steps
- Identified and clarified key project milestones resulting in strategic execution of company mission

Warehouse Manager

April 2008 - December 2009 (1 year 9 months)

- Managed employees to meet manufacturing goals
- Coordinated shipping and receiving employees
- · Projected expected manufacturing goals

- Negotiated materials purchases
- Provided troubleshooting for manufacturing equipment software and hardware

## Education

**Biola University** 

B.S., Organizational Leadership · (2008 - 2010)

Palomar College

Associate of Science, Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse  $\cdot$  (2012 - 2015)